Contact

+918985047521

chiranjeevi.koudi@gmail.com

NRI street, Yousufguda, Hyderbad, Telangana, 500045

www.exploretechspace.com

Social

Linkedin linkedin.com/in/chiranjeevikoudi-0a22aa118

GitHub github.com/chiranjeevikoudi

NPM npmjs.com/~chiru.koudi

Languages

English, Telugu, Hindi

Interests

Machine Learning

Artificial Intelligence

Skills

NodeJS

Python

Datamining

Machine Learning

API Web Services

Loopback, Express Frameworks

MongoDB, MySQL, Neo4j

Android App Development

Java, C

Linux, Windows

Chiranjeevi Koudi

Product Engineer at Way2Online Interactive India Pvt. Ltd. Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Summary

Experienced Product Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Python and NodeJS, Java, Android Development, Machine Learning, and JavaScript. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.) focused in Computer Science and Engineering from Rajiv Gandhi University of Knowledge and Technologies.

Experience

Product Engineer Way2Online Interactive India Pvt. Ltd. December 2016 - Present

Jubilee Hills, Hyderabad

Android Application for Buoy Safety Retrieval Indian National Centre for Ocean Information Services (INCOIS) May 2016 - July 2016 (3 months)

Kukatpally, Hyderabad

Education

Bachelor of Technology (6 Years Integrated Course),

In Computer Science and Engineering. CGPA: 8.81

2013 - 2017

Rajiv Gandhi University of Knowledge and Technologies, Basar

SSC (92.8%) ZPHS Kankal

Awards

Secured mandal 1^{st} Rank, gold medal in SSC

Qualified and got certificates from CodeVita, TalentSprint Coding contests.